Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Advertising Vertical Files, 1950-1994 RL.00660
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 1999-0420
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--State and Local (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--State and Local--AAF (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--State and Local --State Legislature Monitor (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--State and Local--Taxation (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Media (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Media, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Advertising--Media--Buying services (Box 61)
  - Advertising--Media--Comics (Box 61)
  - Advertising--Media--Direct Mail (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Advertising--Media--Direct Mail--Specific Mailing Lists (Box 62)
  - Advertising--Media--Ethnic (Box 62)
  - Advertising--Media--Inserts (Box 63)
  - Advertising--Media--Interactive (Box 63)
  - Advertising--Media--Magazines (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - Advertising--Media--Magazines--Business (Box 63)
  - Advertising--Media--Magazines--Business (Box 64)
  - Advertising--Media--Magazines--Consumer (Box 64)
  - Advertising--Media--Magazines--Consumer statistics (Box 64)
  - Advertising--Media--Magazines--Specific companies (Box 64)
  - Advertising--Media--Magazines--Supplements (Box 64)
  - Advertising--Media--Newspapers, 6 folders (Box 65)
  - Advertising--Media--Newspapers--Statistics (Box 66)
  - Advertising--Media--Newspapers--Supplements (Box 66)
  - Advertising--Media--Newspapers--Pamphlets (Box 66)
  - Advertising--Media--Outdoor (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Advertising--Media--Point of Purchase (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - Advertising--Media--Point of Purchase--Advertising Agencies (Box 67)
  - Advertising--Media--Point of Purchase--Dealer Acceptance (Box 67)
  - Advertising--Media--Point of Purchase--Evaluation (Box 67)
  - Advertising--Media--Point of Purchase--Research (Box 67)
  - Advertising--Media--Point of Purchase--Video (Box 67)
  - Advertising--Media--Radio (Box 68)
  - Advertising--Media--Specialty (Box 69)
  - Advertising--Media--Specialty--Matchbooks (Box 69)
  - Advertising--Media--Television (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Advertising--Media--Television--Cable(2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Advertising--Media--Television--Spot (Box 71)
  - Advertising--Media--Television--Syndication (Box 71)
  - Advertising--Media--Television--Theatre screen (Box 71)
  - Advertising--Media--Television--Transit (Box 72)
  - Advertising--Media--Television--Word of Mouth (Box 72)
  - Advertising--Packaging (2 folders) (Box 72)
  - Advertising--Packaging--Design (Box 72)
  - Advertising--Packaging--Labeling (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Packaging--Labeling--Food (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Packaging--Labeling--Tags (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Packaging--Labeling--Multiple (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Packaging--Labeling--Size (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Packaging--Labeling--Testing (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Product Placements (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Production (Box 73)
  - Advertising--Production--Type faces (Box 74)
  - Advertising--Public Opinion (Box 74)
  - Advertising--Research (3 folders) (Box 74)
  - Advertising--Research (Box 75)
  - Advertising--Research--Bibliography (Box 76)
  - Advertising--Research--Broadcast, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Advertising--Research--Broadcast--TV, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Advertising--Research--Media Evaluation, 4 folders (Box 78)
  - Advertising--Research--Media Evaluation (Box 79)
  - Advertising--Research--Physiological (Box 79)
  - Advertising--Research--Sales effectiveness, 3 folders (Box 79)
  - Advertising--Research--Sales effectiveness, 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Advertising--Research--Sales effectiveness--Bibliography (Box 80)
  - Advertising--Research--Types--Marketing, 3 folders (Box 80)
  - Advertising--Slogans (Box 81)
  - Advertising--Social Aspects (Box 81)
  - Advertising--Target Group, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Advertising--Target Group--Children (5 folders) (Box 82)
  - Advertising--Target Group--Ethnic (Box 83)
  - Advertising--Target Group--Women (2 folders) (Box 83)
  - Advertising--Techniques (Box 84)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Bleed vs. Non-bleed (Box 84)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Color vs. BandW (Box 84)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Comparative, 2 folders (Box 84)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Continuity (Box 84)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Frequency (Box 84)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Headlines and Captions (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Long and short Copy (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Position (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Repetition (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Seasonal (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Size (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Size--Multiple page and spreads (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Size--Small (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Umbrella (Box 85)
  - Advertising--Trademarks, 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--Change (Box 86)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--Creation (Box 86)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--History (Box 86)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--Licensing (Box 87)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--Names (Box 87)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--Names--Creation (Box 87)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--Names--Image (Box 87)
  - Advertising--Trademarks--Specific Company Manuals (Box 87)
  - Advertising--Types, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Advertising--Types--Association (Box 88)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Alcoholic Beverages (Box 89)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Automobiles (Box 89)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Banking (Box 90)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Clothing (Box 90)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Drugs and Toiletries, 3 folders (Box 90)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Electronics (Box 90)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Entertainment, 2 folders (Box 91)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Food (Box 91)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Food Service (Box 91)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Insurance, 2 folders (Box 91)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Petroleum (Box 92)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Tobacco (Box 92)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Transportation (Box 92)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Travel (Box 92)
  - Advertising--Types--By Industry--Utilities (Box 92)
  - Advertising--Types--By Profession (Box 93)
  - Advertising--Types--Classified, 2 folders (Box 93)
  - Advertising--Types--Cooperative, 3 folders (Box 94)
  - Advertising--Types--Cooperative (Box 94)
  - Advertising--Types--Direct response (Box 94)
  - Advertising--Types--Disabled (Box 94)
  - Advertising--Types--Financial (Box 94)
  - Advertising--Types--Generic (Box 95)
  - Advertising--Types--Government (Box 95)
  - Advertising--Types--Humorous (Box 95)
  - Advertising--Types--Industrial (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - Advertising--Types--Industrial (Box 96)
  - Advertising--Types--Institutional, 3 folders (Box 96)
  - Advertising--Types--Institutional--Advocacy (Box 97)
  - Advertising--Types--Political, 2 folders (Box 97)
  - Advertising--Types--Plant City/community (Box 98)
  - Advertising--Types--Public Service, 2 folders (Box 98)
  - Advertising--Types--Retail, 2 folders (Box 98)
  - Advertising--Types--Retail (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Advertising--Types--Subliminal (Box 99)
  - Advertising--Types--Testimonial (Box 99)
  - Advertising--Types--Testimonial--Sports (Box 100)
  - Advertising--Types--Tie-in (Box 100)
  - Advertising--Vocation, 4 folders (Box 100)
  - Advertising--Vocation, 2 folders (Box 101)
  - Advertising--Types--Women (Box 101)